Every day we have a chance to dream big again
毎日、我々は、大きな夢を描くことができます
and make it happen, right?
そして、その夢を現実にするチャンスがあります
What brings me the most joy and passion about this
仕事に取り組む中で、最も大きな喜びとやりがいを感じるのは
is the idea of one table, one team.
「One Table、One Team」という考え方です
Dreaming by myself is just a dream,
一人で見る夢は、ただの夢に過ぎませんが
but dreaming together is the reality
みんなで見る夢は現実になります
Using the SOBABA technology to make the chicken more crispy,
韓国のSOBABAチキンの技術を取り入れ チキンのサクサク感を最大限に引き出しました
and then adding a new sauce flavor for that authenticity.
さらに、韓国本場の新しいソース味を加えました
And then, we have with egg roll, the gochujang works great,
エッグロールを販売する際に、コチュジャンソースを添えると相性抜群です
or any type of to-go execution with a mandu
また、マンドゥをお持ち帰り向けに販売する際も
works great with the gochujang.
このコチュジャンソースは、大きな相乗効果を発揮します
It has a lot of technology
まさに最先端のR&D技術を結集した商品です
@@largest microwaveable pizza.
世界初であり、サイズ規格としても 史上最大級の電子レンジ用ピザです
The spicy-sauced dumplings, which is very much on trend,
こちらは、今トレンドとなっているスパイシーソースマンドゥです
this was something we put through our rapid innovation process.
イノベーティブな高速プロセスによって開発されました
Saucing up these dumplings, a lot of customization happening,
マンドゥにソースをかけて食べるスタイルが大きなブームになっています
and this is turning into one of our No.1's.
これは、当社を代表するヒット商品の一つです
For example, if we’re making fried rice with mandu,
例えば、チャーハンやマンドゥを展開するなら
they must be the best.
それは最高のものでなければなりません
That's my philosophy.
それが私の哲学です
And they must be the first.
常に「最初」でなければなりません
To that end, we must zero in on trends.
そのためには、常にトレンドを先取りする必要があります
We must make the very first product. And if you are sometimes late,
もし「最初」でなければ
if you're the second, then it must be totally different from the existing players.
既存のプレーヤーとは全く違う存在でなければなりません
In other words, we must always be No.1 in the area which we are in.
言い換えると、参入する分野では、常にNo.1を目指すということです
Outstanding competitiveness over our rivals.
競合を圧倒する高い競争力
That's what we must focus on as our target.
それこそが、我々が集中すべきことであり、目標なのです
There's a lot of, you know, various pieces of the CJ world.
CJは、幅広い事業を展開しています
How did teams have worked together across those businesses
異なる事業部のチームがどのように協力し合い
to bring things together?
どのように相乗効果を生み出してきたのか その事例を是非伺いたいと思います
I said based on the lifestyle.
私は、「ライフスタイル」を基盤にしたものだと説明しています
That means, people think it makes sense.
人々もそれを自然に受け止めています
So for example, food and drama doesn't match, people think.
例えば、食とドラマは、一見、接点がないように思われるかもしれませんが
But when you see in K-dramas, they eat ramyun.
K-Dramaを見ながらラーメンを食べますよね？
They use the OLIVE YOUNG cosmetics, right?
ドラマに登場したOLIVE YOUNGのコスメも自然に使っています
So it's all connected.
結局、すべてが密接につながっているのです
Like we all get together and get the synergy.
すべての要素が集まって初めて相乗効果が生まれます
How do you see the leadership capabilities,
リーダーシップのあり方、求める人材像
you know, the right talent profile, and what are those sort of key cultural elements
組織にとって大切な文化的要素について お考えを伺いたいと思います
that really give you confidence,
このチームに限らず、組織の中で、あるチームをご覧になって
whether it be this team or any other team in the organization,
「次のステージへ進む準備ができている」と
that you look at to make sure we're ready for this next step?
どのような要素が揃ったときに確信が持てるのでしょうか？
Something I was a little bit, not surprised, rather really satisfied was
驚いたというより、とても満足したことがあります
all my, using the important keywords or
私が大切にしているキーワード
like what I mentioned through Greg,
今日、グラフを通じて話したことが
was already in your mind.
すでに皆さんの中に根付いていたということです
Those kinds of things made me think, 'Oh, this is real potential.'
その様子を見て 「大きなポテンシャルを持っている」と実感しました
Good attitude and the way you're speaking together is like eager to communicate,
前向きな姿勢 会話を通じて互いに理解しようとする意志があり
eager to make something,
共につくり上げ
and cooperate kind of mind or circumstance, can see it.
協力しようとする意志と雰囲気を感じることができました
I all the time say we are a life company.
私は、常に「ライフスタイル企業」だと紹介しています
As you know that we are not only food
我々は、食品に限らず
but also health and beauty and style and convenience,
健康や美容、スタイル、利便性までを手がけています
so many cultural things.
様々な文化事業にも取り組んでいます
That becomes a very strong weapon to win in the food market, too.
これは、食品市場において非常に強力な武器になります
We are not only just a food company.
我々は、単なる食品メーカーではありません
We are a food company with lifestyle.
ライフスタイルを提案する食品メーカーなのです
That’s a really good chance.
これは、本当に大きなチャンスです
Because, as you know, the K-wave is a huge trend in the States and worldwide,
K-Waveは、アメリカに限らず 世界中で大きなトレンドとなっています
so you have a good chance.
だからこそ、我々には、大きなチャンスがあります
We must do all time the first.
我々は、常に「最初」でなければなりません
We must do the best.
我々は、「最高」にならなければなりません
If you are a little late, you must differentiate.
出遅れたなら、必ず「差別化」を図らなければなりません
That means in the food market, someday you must be a No.1 and the best company
すなわち、食品市場において、いつか我々は、No.1となり 最高のメーカーとなり
and totally different from other companies.
他社とは全く異なる存在でなければならないのです
This is not just a dream.
これは単なる夢ではありません
I believe we can make it.
我々は、必ず実現できると信じています
We have a chance.
我々には、チャンスがあります
We have the weapons.
我々には、武器があります
So we will definitely win.
だからこそ、我々は、必ず勝てると思います
Next year, you will see that.
来年には、我々が食品市場において
We're going to be the company with the highest growth rate in the food market.
最も高い成長率を記録する企業になるのを目にするでしょう
You can do it, right?
皆さん、できますよね？
I think the vision is really to help bring that product to more people in the US.
私のビジョンは、アメリカでもっと多くの人々に韓国料理の魅力を知ってもらうことです
But as we build and innovate,
イノベーションを重ねていけば、人々は我々の商品をより身近に楽しむようになり
and ultimately experiencing Korean food.
最終的に韓国料理を体験するスピードはさらに加速するでしょう
We've become No.1 in frozen pizza in the US,
我々は、米冷凍ピザ市場でNo.1を達成しました
but I'm inspired by further embracing the "we who prove it" mindset
ピザが歩んできた歴史のように、チャレンジ精神を取り入れると
and using that mindset to fuel our growth into the future.
それを未来の成長の原動力になると思います